Communications Workers of America Audio Tape Inventory OH.026
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- Series I: Sound Cassettes, 1952-1987
  - Preservation masters, cassettes NS26A 221-257 (Box 99)
    - CWA Convention: Side 1: Tuesday Morning-13; Side 2: Tuesday Morning-14, 1981 (Cassette NS26A-238)
    - CWA Convention: Side 1: Tuesday Morning-15; Side 2: Tues-16, 1981 (Cassette NS26A-239)
    - CWA Convention: Side 1: Tues-17; Side 2: Tues-18, 1981 (Cassette NS26A-240)
    - CWA Convention: Side 1: Tues-19; Side 2: Tues-20, 1981 (Cassette NS26A-241)
    - CWA Convention: Side 1: Tues-21; Side 2: Tues-22, 1981 (Cassette NS26A-242)
    - CWA Convention: Side 1: Tues-23, Women; Side 2: Tues-24, Women, 1981 (Cassette NS26A-243)
    - CWA Convention: Side 1: 25; Side 2: 26, Women, 1981 (Cassette NS26A-245)
    - CWA Convention: 27, Women (conclusion), 1981 (Cassette NS26A-246)
    - CWA Convention: Side 1: Thurs-29; Side 2: Thurs-30, 1981 (Cassette NS26A-247)
    - CWA Convention: Side 1: Thurs-31; Side 2: Thurs-32, 1981 (Cassette NS26A-248)
    - CWA Convention: Side 1: Thurs-33; Side 2: Thurs-34, 1981 (Cassette NS26A-249)
    - CWA Convention: Side 1: Thurs-35; Side 2: Thurs-36, 1981 (Cassette NS26A-250)
    - CWA Convention: Side 1: Thurs. End, Start Fri-37; Side 2: Fri-38, 1981 (Cassette NS26A-251)
    - CWA Convention: Side 1: 39; Side 2: 40, 1981 (Cassette NS26A-252)
    - CWA Convention: Side 1: 41; Side 2: Fri-42, 1981 (Cassette NS26A-253)
    - CWA Convention: Side 1: Fri-43; Side 2: End Fri-44, 1981 (Cassette NS26A-254)
    - Side A: Radio Interview; Steve Conference on WJMD; Side B: Steve Conference, Jan 27, 1981; Feb 15, 1981 (Cassette NS26A-255)
    - Cramer, Part I, Apr 2, 1981 (Cassette NS26A-256)
    - Cramer, Part II, Tape 1, Apr 2, 1981 (Cassette NS26A-257)
  - Preservation masters, cassettes NS26A 258-284G (Box 100)
    - Cramer, Part II, Tape 2, Apr 2, 1981 (Cassette NS26A-258)
    - Cramer, Part III, Apr 2, 1981 (Cassette NS26A-259)
    - CWA Convention: Side 1: Mon-1; Side 2: Mon-2, President Watts, 1982 (Cassette NS26A-260)
    - CWA Convention: Side 1: Mon-3; Side 2: Mon-4, 1982 (Cassette NS26A-261)
    - CWA Convention: Side 1: Mon-5; Side 2: Mon-6, Press Conference (incomplete), 1982 (Cassette NS26A-262)
    - CWA Convention: Side 1: Mon-7; Side 2: Mon-8, 1982 (Cassette NS26A-263)
    - CWA Convention: Side 1: Mon-9; Side 2: Mon-10, 1982 (Cassette NS26A-264)
    - CWA Convention: Side 1: Mon-11; Side 2: Mon-12, 1982 (Cassette NS26A-265)
    - CWA Convention: Side 1: 15; Side 2: 16, Start Tues, 1982 (Cassette NS26A-266)
    - CWA Convention: Side 1: Tues-17; Side 2: Tues-18, 1982 (Cassette NS26A-267)
    - CWA Convention: Side 1: Tues-19; Side 2: Tues-20, 1982 (Cassette NS26A-268)
    - CWA Convention: Side 1: Tues-21; Side 2: Tues-22, 1982 (Cassette NS26A-269)
    - CWA Convention: Side 1: Tues-23; Side 2: Tues-24, 1982 (Cassette NS26A-270)
    - CWA Convention: Side 1: Wed-25; Side 2: Wed-26, Press Conference with Frazier, 1982 (Cassette NS26A-271)
    - CWA Convention: Side 1: Wed-27; Side 2: Wed-28, 1982 (Cassette NS26A-272)
    - CWA Convention: Side 1: Wed-29; Side 2: Wed-30, 1982 (Cassette NS26A-273)
    - CWA Convention: Side 1: Wed-31; Side 2: Wed-32, 1982 (Cassette NS26A-274)
    - CWA Convention: Side 1: Mon-33; Side 2: Mon-34, 1982 (Cassette NS26A-275)
    - CWA Convention: Side 1: Wed-35, Thurs; Side 2: Thurs-36, 1982 (Cassette NS26A-276)
    - CWA Convention: Side 1: Thurs-37; Side 2: Thurs-38, 1982 (Cassette NS26A-277)
    - CWA Convention: Side 1: Thurs-39; Side 2: Thurs-40, 1982 (Cassette NS26A-278)
    - CWA Convention: Side 1: Thurs-41; Side 2: Thurs-42, 1982 (Cassette NS26A-279)
    - CWA Convention: Side 1: Thurs-43; Side 2: Thurs-44, 1982 (Cassette NS26A-280)
    - CWA Convention: Side 1: Thurs-45; Side 2: Thurs-46, 1982 (Cassette NS26A-281)
    - CWA Executive Board Meetings, Jan 13, 1982 (Cassette NS26A-282)
    - CWA Executive Board Meetings, Feb 1, 1982 (Cassette NS26A-283)
    - CWA Executive Board Meetings, Nov 3, 1982 (Cassette NS26A-284)
    - CWA Committee on the Future Special Convention (Philadelphia, PA): Monday 1-2, Mar 28, 1983 (Cassette NS26A-284)
    - CWA Committee on the Future Special Convention (Philadelphia, PA): Monday 3-4, Mar 28, 1983 (Cassette NS26A-284)
    - CWA Committee on the Future Special Convention (Philadelphia, PA): Monday 5 (end a.m.)-6 (start p.m.), Mar 28, 1983 (Cassette NS26A-284)
    - CWA Committee on the Future Special Convention (Philadelphia, PA): Monday 7-8, Mar 28, 1983 (Cassette NS26A-284)
    - CWA Committee on the Future Special Convention (Philadelphia, PA): Monday 9-10, Mar 28, 1983 (Cassette NS26A-284)
    - CWA Committee on the Future Special Convention (Philadelphia, PA): Monday 11-12 (end Mon), Mar 28, 1983 (Cassette NS26A-284)
    - CWA Committee on the Future Special Convention (Philadelphia, PA): Tuesday 13 (start Tues)-14, Mar 29, 1983 (Cassette NS26A-284)
  - Preservation masters, cassettes NS26A 284H-312 (Box 101)
    - CWA Committee on the Future Special Convention (Philadelphia, PA): Tuesday 15-16, Mar 29, 1983 (Cassette NS26A-284)
    - CWA Committee on the Future Special Convention (Philadelphia, PA): Tuesday 17-18 (end a.m.), Mar 29, 1983 (Cassette NS26A-284)
    - CWA Committee on the Future Special Convention (Philadelphia, PA): Tuesday 19 (start p.m.)-20, Mar 29, 1983 (Cassette NS26A-284)
    - CWA Committee on the Future Special Convention (Philadelphia, PA): Tuesday 21-22, Mar 29, 1983 (Cassette NS26A-284)
    - CWA Committee on the Future Special Convention (Philadelphia, PA): Tuesday 23-24, Mar 29, 1983 (Cassette NS26A-284)
    - CWA Committee on the Future Special Convention (Philadelphia, PA): Tuesday 25-26, Mar 29, 1983 (Cassette NS26A-284)
    - CWA Executive Board Meetings, Aug 2, 1983 (Cassette NS26A-285)
    - CWA Executive Board Meetings, Aug 2, 1983 (Cassette NS26A-286)
    - CWA Executive Board Meetings, Aug 2, 1983 (Cassette NS26A-287)
    - CWA Executive Board Meetings, Apr 13, 1984 (Cassette NS26A-288)
    - CWA Convention: Highlights, Morton Bahr, Jun 7, 1905 (Cassette NS26A-288)
    - CWA Convention: Highlights, Morton Bahr, Feb 15, 1985 (Cassette NS26A-289)
    - CWA Convention: Monday, Apr 21, 1986 (Cassette NS26A-290)
    - CWA Convention: Monday, Apr 21, 1986 (Cassette NS26A-291)
    - CWA Convention: Monday, Apr 21, 1986 (Cassette NS26A-292)
    - CWA Convention: Monday, Apr 21, 1986 (Cassette NS26A-293)
    - CWA Convention: Monday, Apr 21, 1986 (Cassette NS26A-294)
    - CWA Convention: Tuesday, Apr 22, 1986 (Cassette NS26A-295)
    - CWA Convention: Tuesday, Apr 22, 1986 (Cassette NS26A-296)
    - CWA Convention: Tuesday, Apr 22, 1986 (Cassette NS26A-297)
    - CWA Convention: Tuesday, Apr 22, 1986 (Cassette NS26A-298)
    - CWA Convention: Tuesday, Apr 22, 1986 (Cassette NS26A-299)
    - CWA Convention: Wednesday, Apr 23, 1986 (Cassette NS26A-300)
    - CWA Convention: Wednesday, Apr 23, 1986 (Cassette NS26A-301)
    - CWA Convention: Wednesday, Apr 23, 1986 (Cassette NS26A-302)
    - CWA Convention: Wednesday-Thursday, Apr 23-24, 1986 (Cassette NS26A-303)
    - CWA Convention: Thursday, Apr 24, 1986 (Cassette NS26A-304)
    - CWA Convention: Thursday, Apr 24, 1986 (Cassette NS26A-305)
    - CWA Executive Board Meetings, Jun 24, 1986 (Cassette NS26A-306)
    - CWA Executive Board Meetings, Jun 26, 1986 (Cassette NS26A-307)
    - CWA Convention: Rally 1-2, 1987 (Cassette NS26A-308)
    - CWA Convention: Rally 3-4, 1987 (Cassette NS26A-309)
    - CWA Convention: Press Conference Mon, 1987 (Cassette NS26A-310)
    - CWA Convention: Monday 1-2, 1987 (Cassette NS26A-311)
    - CWA Convention: Monday 4-5, 1987 (Cassette NS26A-312)
  - Preservation masters, cassettes NS26A 313-332, 500-513 (Box 102)
    - CWA Convention: Monday 5-6, 1987 (Cassette NS26A-313)
    - CWA Convention: Monday 7-8, 1987 (Cassette NS26A-314)
    - CWA Convention: Monday 9-10, 1987 (Cassette NS26A-315)
    - CWA Convention: Monday 11-12, 1987 (Cassette NS26A-316)
    - CWA Convention: Mon-Tues 13-14, 1987 (Cassette NS26A-317)
    - CWA Convention: Tuesday 15-16, 1987 (Cassette NS26A-318)
    - CWA Convention: Tuesday 17-18, 1987 (Cassette NS26A-319)
    - CWA Convention: Tuesday 19-20, 1987 (Cassette NS26A-320)
    - CWA Convention: Tues-Wed 23-24, 1987 (Cassette NS26A-321)
    - CWA Convention: Wednesday 25-26, 1987 (Cassette NS26A-322)
    - CWA Convention: Wednesday 27-28, 1987 (Cassette NS26A-323)
    - CWA Convention: Wednesday 29-30, 1987 (Cassette NS26A-324)
    - CWA Convention: Wednesday 31-32, 1987 (Cassette NS26A-325)
    - CWA Convention: Wednesday 33-34, 1987 (Cassette NS26A-326)
    - CWA Convention: Thursday 35-36, 1987 (Cassette NS26A-327)
    - CWA Convention: Thursday 37-38, 1987 (Cassette NS26A-328)
    - CWA Convention: Thursday 39-40, 1987 (Cassette NS26A-329)
    - CWA Convention: Thursday 41-42, 1987 (Cassette NS26A-330)
    - CWA Convention, 1987 (Cassette NS26A-331)
    - CWA Convention, 1987 (Cassette NS26A-332)
    - C-2, undated (Cassette NS26A-500)
    - Cas 9-A: End Tuesday, undated (Cassette NS26A-501)
    - Cas 10: Wednesday, undated (Cassette NS26A-502)
    - Cas 11, undated (Cassette NS26A-503)
    - Cas 12, undated (Cassette NS26A-504)
    - Cas 13, undated (Cassette NS26A-505)
    - Cas 14, undated (Cassette NS26A-506)
    - Cas 15, undated (Cassette NS26A-507)
    - Cas 18, undated (Cassette NS26A-508)
    - Cas 19, undated (Cassette NS26A-509)
    - Charter Review Committee, undated (Cassette NS26A-510)
    - Charter Review Committee, undated (Cassette NS26A-511)
    - CWA Audio Bargaining Report (Justice!): AT&T/RBOC Bargaining Councils (Jan 6-10), undated (Cassette NS26A-512)
    - CWA Audio Bargaining Report (Justice!): AT&T/RBOC Bargaining Councils (Jan 6-10), undated (Cassette NS26A-513)
  - Preservation masters, cassettes NS26A 514-549 (Box 103)
    - CWA Convention (Cassette Sides 3-4): Women's Act Conference, undated (Cassette NS26A-514)
    - CWA Convention (Cassette Sides 5-6): Weber-Beirne, Part 1; Monday Morning, Part 2, undated (Cassette NS26A-515)
    - CWA Convention (Cassette Sides 7-8): Beirne on Monday Morning-Afternoon, undated (Cassette NS26A-516)
    - CWA Convention (Cassette Sides 9-10): Monday Afternoon, undated (Cassette NS26A-517)
    - CWA Convention (Cassette Sides 11-12): Filby, Monday Morning; Monday Afternoon, Start "Bowl", undated (Cassette NS26A-518)
    - CWA Convention (Cassette Sides 13-14): Bowl, Part 2; Tuesday, Part 1, undated (Cassette NS26A-519)
    - CWA Convention (Cassette Sides 15-16): Tuesday, Part 2-3, undated (Cassette NS26A-520)
    - CWA Convention (Cassette Sides 17-18): Tuesday, Part 4-5, undated (Cassette NS26A-521)
    - CWA Convention (Cassette Sides 19-20): Tuesday-Wednesday, Parts 1-2, undated (Cassette NS26A-522)
    - CWA Convention (Cassette Sides 21-22): Wednesday, Part 3-4, undated (Cassette NS26A-523)
    - CWA Convention (Cassette Sides 23-24): Wednesday, Part 5-6, undated (Cassette NS26A-524)
    - CWA Convention (Cassette Sides 25-26): Wednesday, Part 7-8; Beirne, Close, undated (Cassette NS26A-525)
    - CWA Convention (Thurs. Morning): Dr. Sue Steinmetz; Biscardi, undated (Cassette NS26A-526)
    - CWA Convention (Thurs. Morning): Lucis Webb; Panel, undated (Cassette NS26A-527)
    - CWA Convention: President Watts with Questions & Answers, undated (Cassette NS26A-528)
    - CWA Convention Music, undated (Cassette NS26A-529)
    - CWA Convention Music, undated (Cassette NS26A-530)
    - CWA Emergency PSA's (English & Spanish), undated (Cassette NS26A-531)
    - CWA Executive Board, undated (Cassette NS26A-532)
    - CWA Executive Board, undated (Cassette NS26A-533)
    - CWA Executive Board, undated (Cassette NS26A-534)
    - CWA Executive Board, undated (Cassette NS26A-535)
    - CWA Executive Board: Bargaining Discussion, undated (Cassette NS26A-536)
    - CWA Executive Board: Bargaining Discussion, undated (Cassette NS26A-537)
    - CWA Executive Board: Discussion on Special Convention, undated (Cassette NS26A-538)
    - CWA Executive Board Meetings (Aug 2, Aug 4), undated (Cassette NS26A-539)
    - CWA Executive Board Meetings (Aug 21), undated (Cassette NS26A-540)
    - CWA Executive Board Meetings (Aug 21), undated (Cassette NS26A-541)
    - CWA Executive Board Meetings (Aug 21), undated (Cassette NS26A-542)
    - CWA Radio Promotion, undated (Cassette NS26A-543)
    - CWA Song, undated (Cassette NS26A-544)
    - CWA Song, undated (Cassette NS26A-545)
    - CWA Song, undated (Cassette NS26A-546)
    - CWA Song (Official) "We Stand Together": Short & Long Vocal & Instrumental Versions, undated (Cassette NS26A-547)
    - CWA Song (Official) "We Stand Together": Short & Long Vocal & Instrumental Versions, undated (Cassette NS26A-548)
    - CWA Spots: 9 Thru 15, Flight II, undated (Cassette NS26A-549)
  - Preservation masters, cassettes NS26A 550-578 (Box 104)
    - CWA Spots (2nd Set), undated (Cassette NS26A-550)
    - CWA Spots (Upstate New York), undated (Cassette NS26A-551)
    - Defense Fund, undated (Cassette NS26A-552)
    - Defense Fund, undated (Cassette NS26A-553)
    - 4309 Appeal, undated (Cassette NS26A-554)
    - Louisiana Radio Review, undated (Cassette NS26A-555)
    - New York T.P. ("R Rated"), undated (Cassette NS26A-556)
    - Opening of AT&T Talks (Apr 2), undated (Cassette NS26A-557)
    - PTT-11, undated (Cassette NS26A-558)
    - PTTI: Berlin Conference with Beirne, undated (Cassette NS26A-559)
    - Radio Broadcasts: CWA Local Radio Network- Side A: Introduction; Side B: Commercials, undated (Cassette NS26A-560)
    - Radio Broadcasts: Voter Registration Radio Ads, with Introduction, undated (Cassette NS26A-561)
    - Rewiring Your World: Editions I-II with Martin Agronsky, undated (Cassette NS26A-562)
    - Rewiring Your World: Editions I-II with Martin Agronsky, undated (Cassette NS26A-563)
    - Rewiring Your World: Programs 1-6 with Martin Agronsky, undated (Cassette NS26A-564)
    - Rewiring Your World: Programs 1-6 with Martin Agronsky, undated (Cassette NS26A-565)
    - Rewiring Your World: Winners & Losers in the Information Age, undated (Cassette NS26A-566)
    - Rewiring Your World: Winners & Losers in the Information Age, undated (Cassette NS26A-567)
    - Sales Bargaining Unit Meeting: Knecht Comments, undated (Cassette NS26A-568)
    - Solidarity Planning (Jan 30), undated (Cassette NS26A-569)
    - "Songs of Working People", undated (Cassette NS26A-570)
    - Union Builders Rally: R-10 Monday Evening & Rally, undated (Cassette NS26A-571)
    - Union Builders Rally: R-11 Monday Evening & Rally, undated (Cassette NS26A-572)
    - Union Builders Rally: R-12 Monday Evening & Rally, undated (Cassette NS26A-573)
    - "Working For You in California", undated (Cassette NS26A-574)
    - "Working For You in California", undated (Cassette NS26A-575)
    - AT&T: Finances, undated (Cassette NS26A-576)
    - The Letters of Ed Schultz, undated (Cassette NS26A-577)
    - Legislative Conference: Election of Delegates (Dec 11), undated (Cassette NS26A-578)